Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Shimada, Haruo's "Japan's" - Rewarding Work. (Box 23)
  - Stepp, John R., "Productivity and Cooperation: A Partnership for the 1980's and Beyond", Publication (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation: A Framework for Economic Development, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Stepp, John R., "Remarks", Publication (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: Productivity and Cooperation: A Partnership for the 1980's and Beyond, Publication (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Stepp, John R., "Remarks", Publication (Box 23, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Stepp, John R., "Remarks", Publication (Box 23, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Stepp, John R., "The Diffusion of Innovative Work Arrangements", Publication (Box 23, Folder 92)
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - Stepp, John R., "Turbulent Era Brings Change to Labor Relations", Publication (Box 23, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: The Diffusion of Innovative Work Arrangements, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Stern, James L. and Craig Olson, "The Propensity of Local Government Employees to Strike", Publication (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: Turbulent Era Brings Chagnge to Labor Relations, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Stewart, Steve R., "Case Study 60--Sabine River Works", Publication (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Item 1: The Propensity of Local Government Employees to Strike, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 95)
      Author: James L. Stern and Craig Olson
  - Stewart, Steve R., "Firs National Bank of Chicago: Commitment to Quality Cuts Costs, Adds Customers", Publication (Box 23, Folder 96)
    - Item 1: Case Study 60- Sabine River Works, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 96)
      Author: Steve R. Stewart
  - Stewart, Stephen R., "Case Study 65--Scottsdale Arizona", Publication (Box 23, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: First National Bank of Chicago: Commitment to Quality Cuts Costs, Adds Customers, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Stewart, Stephen R., "Case Study 76--Ethyl Corporation", Publication (Box 23, Folder 98)
    - Item 1: Case Study 65- Scottsdale Arizona, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 98)
      Author: Stephen R. Stewart
  - Stewart, Thomas A., "The Search for the Organization of Tomorrow", Publication (Box 23, Folder 99)
    - Item 1: Case Study 76- Ethyl Corporation, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - Stieber, Jack and Liba Paukert, "Manpower and Technological Change in Czechoslovakia", Publication (Box 23, Folder 100)
    - Item 1: GE Keeps Those Ideas Coming, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 100)
      Author: Thomas A. Stewart
  - Stockton, William, "Tearing Apart Eastern Airlines", Publication (Box 23, Folder 101)
    - Item 1: The Search for the Organization of Tomorrow, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 101)
  - Stoever, William A., "Japanese Boss, American Employees", Publication (Box 23, Folder 102)
    - Item 1: Manpower and Technological Change in Czechoslovakia, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 102)
      Author: Jack Stieber and Liba Paukert
  - Stokes, Bruce, Worker Participation-Productivity and the Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 23, Folder 103)
    - Item 1: Tearing Apart Eastern Airlines, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 103)
      Author: William Stockton
  - Stone, Katherine Van Wezel, "Labor and Corporate Structure: Changing Conceptions and Emerging Possibilities", Publication (Box 23, Folder 104)
    - Item 1: Japanese Boss, American Employees, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 104)
      Author: William A. Stoever
  - Stone, Nan. "Does Business Have Any Business in Education?", Publication (Box 23, Folder 105)
    - Item 1: Worker Participation- Productivity and the Quality of Work Life, 1978; Publication (Box 23, Folder 105)
      Author: Bruce Stokes
  - Streek, Wolfgang. "The New Industrial Relations: A Strategic Role for Unions in Vocational Training?", Publication (Box 23, Folder 106)
    - Item 1: Labor and Corporate Structure: Changing Conceptions and Emerging Possibilities, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 106)
      Author: Katherine Van Wezel Stone
  - Spitz, Janet. "Promotion, Reward and Selectively Measured Performance", Publication (Box 23, Folder 107)
    - Item 1: Does Business Have Any Business in Education?, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 107)
      Author: Nan Stone
  - "Stonewalling Plant Democracy", Publication (Box 23, Folder 108)
    - Item 1: The New Industrial Relations: A Strategic Role for Unions in Vocational Training?, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 108)
      Author: Wolfgang Streek
  - Stovicek, Don, "Manufacturing Excellence Awards: The Five Winners", Publication (Box 23, Folder 109)
    - Item 1: Promotion, Reward and Selectively Measured Performance, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 109)
      Author: Janet Spitz
  - Stralkowski, Michael C. and Alexander S. Bilcon, "Partnering: A Strategic Approach to Productivity Improvement", Publication (Box 23, Folder 110)
    - Item 1: Stonewalling Plant Democracy, 1977; Publication (Box 23, Folder 110)
  - Strassman, Paul, "The Office of the Future: Information Management for the New Age", Publication (Box 23, Folder 111)
    - Item 1: Manufacturing Excellence Awards: The Five Winners, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 111)
      Author: Don Stovicek
  - Stratton, Donald A. "SorageTek and Excellence Through Quality", Publication (Box 23, Folder 112)
    - Item 1: Partnering: A Strategic Approach to Productivity Improvement, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 112)
      Author: Michael C. Stralkowski and S. Alexander Billon
  - Strauss, George, "Industrial Relations: Time of Change", Publication (Box 23, Folder 113)
    - Item 1: The Office of the Future: Information Management for the New Age, 1980; Publication (Box 23, Folder 113)
      Author: Paul Strassman
  - Strauss, George, "Participatory and Gainsharing Systems: History and Hope", Publication (Box 23, Folder 114)
    - Item 1: StorageTek and Excellence Through Quality, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 114)
      Author: A. Donald Stratton
  - Strauss, George, "Workers' Participation Symposium Introduction", Publication (Box 23, Folder 115)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations: Time of Change, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 115)
      Author: George Strauss
  - Strautberg, Susan S., "Status Report: The Corporation and Trends in Family Issues", Publication (Box 23, Folder 116)
    - Item 1: Participatory and Gainsharing Systems: History and Hope, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 116)
  - Staw, Barry M., "Organizational Psychology and the Pursuit of the Productive/Happy Worker", Publication (Box 23, Folder 117)
    - Item 1: Workers' Participation: Symposium Introduction, 1979; Publication (Box 23, Folder 117)
  - Straw, Ronnie J. and Lorel E. Foged, Final Report: CWA/ AT&T Conference on New Technology and Work Innovations, Publication (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - Item 1: Status Report: The Corporation and Trends in Family Issues, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 118)
      Author: Susan S. Stautberg
  - Straw, Ronnie J. and Charles C. Hecksher, "QWL: New Working Relationships in the Communication Industry", Publication (Box 23, Folder 119)
    - Item 1: Organizational Psychology and the Pursuit of the Happy/Productive Worker, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 119)
  - Streek, Wolfgang The New Industrial Relations: A Strategic Role for Unions in Vocational Training?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 120)
    - Item 1: Final Report: CWA/AT&T Conference on New Technology and Work Innovations, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 120)
      Author: Ronnie J. Straw and Lorel E. Foged
  - Street, John, "Socialist Arguments for Industrial Development", Publication (Box 23, Folder 121)
    - Item 1: QWL: New Working Relationships in the Communication Industry, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 121)
      Author: Ronnie J. Straw and Charles C. Hecksher
  - Striner, Herbert E., "Retraining as a National Capital Investment", Publication (Box 23, Folder 122)
    - Item 1: The New Industrial Relations: A Strategic Role for Unions in Vocational Training?, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 122)
      Author: Wolfgang Streeck
  - Strohmeyer, John, "The Agonizing Ordeal of a One-Company Town", Publication (Box 23, Folder 123)
    - Item 1: Socialist Arguments for Industrial Democracy, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 123)
      Author: John Street
  - "Stunning Turnaround at Tarrytown", Publication (Box 23, Folder 124)
    - Item 1: Retraining as a National Capital Investment, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 124)
      Author: Herbert E. Striner
  - Subcommittee on Employment and Productivity, Productivity and the American Economy: Report on Findings, Publication (Box 23, Folder 125)
    - Item 1: The Agonizing Ordeal of a One-Company Town, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 125)
      Author: John Strohmeyer
  - Subcommittee on Science, Research and Technology, The Human Factor in Innovation and Productivity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 126)
    - Item 1: Stunning Turnaround at Tarrytown, 1980; Publication (Box 23, Folder 126)
  - Sullivan, Jeremiah J., "A Critique of Theory Z", Publication (Box 23, Folder 127)
    - Item 1: Productivity and the American Economy: Report and Findings, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 127)
  - Sultan, Paul E., "From Adversarialism to Cooperation: Is this Trip Necessary?", Publication (Box 23, Folder 128)
    - Item 1: The Human Factor in Innovation and Productivity, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 128)
  - Sultan, Paul E., "It's a New World Out There", Publication (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Item 1: A Critique of Theory Z, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 129)
      Author: Jeremiah J. Sullivan
  - Sultan, Paul, "Labor Management Cooperation: Is an Ideological Retrofit Possible?", Publication (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - Item 1: From Adversarialism to Cooperation: Is this Trip Necessary?, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 130)
      Author: Paul E. Sultan
  - Sulzner, George T., "The Impact of Labor-Management Cooperation Committees on Personnel Policies and Practices at Twenty Federal Bargaining Units", Publication (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Item 1: It's A New World Out There, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 131)
  - Summanth, David J., "Productivity Indicators Used By Major U.S. Non-Industrial Corporations", Publication (Box 23, Folder 132)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation: Is an Ideological Retrofit Possible?, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 132)
      Author: Paul Sultan
  - Sunderland, Kaye McDonald, "No Easy Answers: Obstacles to Collaborative Bargaining in Teacher Negotiations", Publication (Box 23, Folder 133)
    - Item 1: The Impact of Labor-Management Cooperation Committees on Personnel Policies and Practices at Twenty Federal Bargaining Units, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 133)
      Author: George T. Sulzner
  - Sundqvist, Ulf, New Technologies in the 1990s: A Socio-Economic Strategy, Publication (Box 23, Folder 134)
    - Item 1: Productivity Indicators Used by Major U.S. Non-Industrial Corporations, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 134)
      Author: David J. Sumanth
  - Surpin, Rick, Enterprise Development and Worker Ownership: A Strategy for Community Economic Development, Publication (Box 23, Folder 135)
    - Item 1: No Easy Answers: Obstacles to Collaborative Bargaining in Teacher Negotiations, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 135)
      Author: Kaye McDonald Sunderland
  - Susman, Gerald, "Job Enlargement: Effects of Culture on Worker Responses", Publication (Box 23, Folder 136)
    - Item 1: New Technologies in the 1990s: A Socio-Economic Strategy, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 136)
      Author: Ulf Sundqvist
  - Susman, Gerald I., A Summary of the Role of Third Parties in Labor-Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 23, Folder 137)
    - Item 1: Enterprise Development and Worker Ownership: A Strategy for Community Economic Development, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 137)
      Author: Rick Surpin
  - Sutherland, Elyse A., Ph.D., "Helping QWL Teams Identify Work-Related Issues", Publication (Box 23, Folder 138)
    - Item 1: Job Enlargement: Effects of Culture on Worker Responses, 1973; Publication (Box 23, Folder 138)
      Author: Gerald Susman
  - Swartz, Gerald E. and Vivian C. Comstock, "One Firm's Experience With Quality Circles", Publication (Box 23, Folder 139)
    - Item 1: A Summary of the Role of Third Parties in Labor-Management Cooperation Endeavors, 1978; Publication (Box 23, Folder 139)
      Author: Gerald I. Susman
  - Swedish Center for Quality of Working Life, Annual Report 1980/81 and Operations Schedule 1981-1983, Publication (Box 23, Folder 140)
    - Item 1: Helping QWL Teams Identify Work-Related Issues, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 140)
      Author: Elyse A. Sutherland
  - The Swedish Labor Market 1986-87, Annual Report of the Swedish Labor Market Administration, Publication (Box 23, Folder 141)
    - Item 1: One Firm's Experience with Quality Circles, 1979; Publication (Box 23, Folder 141)
      Author: Gerald E. Swartz and Vivian C. Comstock
  - Swedish Work Environment Fund, Labor Law Research: Present Situation and Future Developments, Publication (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - Item 1: Annual Report 1980/1981 and Operations Schedule 1981-1983, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - "Rewarding Work", Publication (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - Item 1: The Swedish Labour Market 1986-1987, Publication (Box 23, Folder 143)
- Sweden Works - Trist, Eric., Publication (Box 24)
  - Sweden Works: Industry in Transition, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Sweden Works: Industry in Transition, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Swedish Programme on New Technology and Human Resources", Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Swedish Programme on New Technology and Human Resources, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Sweeney, Kevin M., Building and Effective Labor-Management Safety and Health Committee, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Building an Effective Labor-Management Safety and Health Committee, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Author: Kevin M. Sweeney
  - Sweetland, John, Highlights of the Literature: Managerial Productivity, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: Managerial Productivity, 1978; Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Author: John Sweetland
  - Sweetland, John, Highlights of the Literature: Mid-Career Perspectives: The Middle-Aged and Older Population, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: Mid-Career Perspectives: The Middle-Aged and Older Population, 1978; Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Swiercz, Paul Michael and Lorentzen, John F., "Cutting Labor Costs: The Buyout Alternative", Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Cutting Labor Costs: The Buyout Alternative, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Author: Paul Michael Swiercz and John F. Lorentzen
  - Swindensky, Robert/Vanderkamp, John, "A Micro-econometric Analysis of Strike Activity in Canada", Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: A Micro-economic Analysis of Strike Activity in Canada, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Author: Robert Swidinsky and John Vanderkamp
  - Swinney, Dan "Worker Ownership", Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Worker Ownership, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Author: Dan Swinney
  - Szabo, Joan C. "Finding the Right Workers", Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Finding the Right Workers, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Author: Joan C. Szabo
  - Tacy, Lynne, "Trends in Industrial Democracy in Western Europe", Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Trends in Industrial Democracy in Western Europe, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Author: Lynne Tacy
  - TASC, Some Social Consequences of the Dana Corporation's Plant Closing in Edgerton, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Some Social Consequences of the Dana Corporation's Plant Closing in Edgerton, 1980; Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Taft, Philip. "On the Origins of Business Unionism", Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: On the Origins of Business Unionism, 1963; Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
      Author: Philip Taft
  - Tagliaferri, Louis E., "As 'Quality Circles' Fade, a Bank Tries 'Top-Down' Teamwork", Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: As Quality Circles' Fade, a Bank Tries Top-Down Teamwork, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Author: Louis E. Tagliaferri
  - Taira, Koji, "Labor Productivity and Industrial Relations in the United States and Japan", Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Labor Productivity and Industrial Relations in the United States and Japan, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
      Author: Koji Taira
  - Taira, Koji. "Japanese 'Enterprise Unionism' and Interfirm Wage Structure", Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Japanese 'Enterprise Unionism' and Interfirm Wage Structure, 1961; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Takeuchi, Hirotaka, "Productivity: Learning from the Japanese", Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Productivity: Learning from the Japanese, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
      Author: Hirotaka Takeuchi
  - Takezawa, Shin-ichi, "The Quality of Working Life: Trends in Japan", Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: The Quality of Working Life: Trends in Japan, 1976; Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
      Author: Shin-ichi Takezawa
  - Talbot, Richard P. and Robert L. Geyer, "Comparing Cross-Cultural Thinking Preferences", Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Comparing Cross-Cultural Thinking Preferences, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
      Author: Richard P. Talbot and Robert L. Geyer
  - Talbot, Vernon G. and Linda Byrum Oldham, "The Future of Quality of Working Life", Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: The Future of Quality of Working Life, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
      Author: Vernon G. Talbot and Linda Byrum Oldham
  - Tamarkin, Bob and Lisa Gross, "Starting Over in Chicago", Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Starting Over in Chicago, 1980; Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
      Author: Bob Tamarkin and Lisa Gross
  - Tanaka, Fujio John, "Lifetime Employment in Japan", Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Lifetime Employment in Japan, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
      Author: Fujio John Tanaka
  - Tanner, Lucretia Dewey and Jerome R. Barret, "Bargaining in the Health Care Industry", Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Bargaining in the Health Care Industry, Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
      Author: Lucretia Dewey Tanner and Jerome T. Barrett
  - Tanner, William R., "Robotics: Their Sociological Implications", Publication (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Robotics: Their Sociological Implications, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 23)
      Author: William R. Tanner
  - Tanriverdi, Nail, and Yazir, Suleyman, "Collective Bargaining in Turkey: Recent Trends and Problems", Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in Turkey: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
      Author: Nail Tanriverdi and Suleyman Yazir
  - Taplin, Polly, "ESOPs Meet Needs of a Variety of Companies", Publication (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: ESOPs Meet the Needs of a Variety of Companies, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 25)
      Author: Polly Taplin
  - Taplin, Polly T., "Philosophically and Practically, Stock Ownership Proves Worthwhile for Company and Employees", Publication (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Philosophically and Practically, Stock Ownership Proves Worthwhile for Company and Employees, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 26)
      Author: Polly T. Taplin
  - The Tarkenton Productivity Update, Publication (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Knowledge Worker Performance Measurement, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - The Tarkenton Productivity Update, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Participative Management Systems, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - The Tarkenton Productivity Update, Publication (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Productivity- The Essential Ingredients for Success, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - The Tarkenton Productivity Update, Publication (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Translating Productivity Strategies into Action: A Case Study, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Task Force on Education for Economic Growth, Action in the States, Publication (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Action in the States, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Task Force on Micro-electronics and Employment, Publication (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: In the Chips: Opportunities, People, Partnerships, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Task Force on Rail Transportation, Labor/Management Cooperation in Multicarrier Rail Terminals, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Labor/Management Cooperation in Multicarrier Rail Terminals, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Tavernier, Gerard, "Awakening a Sleeping Giant", Publication (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Awakening a Sleeping GiantFord's Employee Involvement Program, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 34)
      Author: Gerard Tavernier
  - Taylor, Alex III. "The Road Ahead at General Motors", Publication (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: The Road Ahead at General Motors, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 35)
      Author: Alex Taylor III
  - Taylor, Alex III. "A U.S. Style Shakeup at Honda", Publication (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: A US-Style Shakeup at Honda, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Taylor, Dennis W., "Information and Decision Sharing with Employees", Publication (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Information and Decision Sharing With Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 37)
      Author: Dennis W. Taylor
  - Taylor, George W., "Public Employment: Strikes or Procedures?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Public Employment: Strikes or Procedures?, 1967; Publication (Box 24, Folder 38)
      Author: George W. Taylor
  - Taylor, Ian, "The Strategic Input of Information Technology on Britain's Leading Businesses: Myth and Reality", Publication (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: The Strategic Input of Information Technology on Britain's Leading Businesses: Myth and Reality, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 39)
      Author: Ian Taylor
  - Taylor, James C. and Robert A. Asadorian, "The Implementation of Excellence: STS Management", Publication (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: The Implementation of Excellence: STS Management, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 40)
      Author: James C. Taylor and Robert A. Asadorian
  - Taylor, Jay How Safe are Pension Funds?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: How Safe Are Pension Funds?, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 41)
      Author: Jay Taylor
  - Technology Management Group, In Support of Strategies for Technology Assistance Programs: Assisting Small and Medium Sized Manufacturers, Publication (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: In Support of Strategies for Technology Assistance Programs: Assisting Small and Medium Sized Manufacturers, Publication (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Teicher, Julian, "Worker Involvement: An Analysis of SECV Working Parties--A Comment", Publication (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Worker Involvement: An Analysis of SECV Working Parties- A Comment, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 43)
      Author: Julian Teicher
  - Teitelbaum, Richard S. "Are Times Tough? Here's the Answer", Publication (Box 24, Folder 44)